{
    "id": "5f21b87ada014fc8864ff53378a3309e",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The boy ran …………………………….. the street.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dda3bd6058e147efa46d1db4803421a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "He walked ………………………….. the building.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "around",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c32dfe261e54786a1121fc2f32a4c0d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train goes ……………………….. a tunnel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "through",
                "along"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e99ab31fd2a4384bf8636d246fedc06"
        },
        {
            "question": "I walked …………………………….. the river bank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "along"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "08578c1f0aaf44e68a85f8b70ea999ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is standing …………………………. the gate?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4334585d712e45568fde606fc9c25260"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your glasses are ………………………….. your nose.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7060661814b940d196ffa38825e7af3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat is hiding ………………………….. the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "behind",
                "below",
                "under"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d018daa2930245d8af899abf7f9931f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Come and stand ………………………….. me, Jane.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "in front of",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a9e10b337d474fa5986e1b333ae1f520"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog came running …………………………… its master, wagging its tail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a977faa578d493484bbc999305095ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "They walked …………………………………. each other.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "towards"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f3f5e73fd785432d9c17ccea1d05c694"
        }
    ]
}